>> Kyle Simpson: 如果您在此情况下使用双等号，那么在此情况下，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If you use a double
equals between, in this case, a number and
一个包含数字的数组。
an array that holds the number.
这真是太可怕了
This is a really terrible idea.
您不应该编写将原语与类似数组进行比较的代码。
You should never write code that compares
a primitive to an array like that.
但如果你有原因的话如果你写了一个
But if you did, if for some reason
you wrote a function that couldn't
控制某人是否通过了数字或
control whether somebody
passed a number or
一个数字的数组，它会被强迫地工作吗 ?
an array with a number in it,
would it work coercively?
在这宗个案中，是，但是否应该这样做 ?
In this particular case,
yes, but should it?
还有比工作更重要的原因吗
Ooh, and why is more important,
even, than does it work?
为什么这一工作 ?
Why would this one work?
为什么一个数字在某种程度上被强迫等同于一个持有该数字的数组 ?
Why would a number somehow be coercively
equal to an array holding that number?
而且只有在那个阵列只有一个号码的情况下
And certainly only in the case where
that array only has the single number,
如果有多个号码不是吗
not if it had multiple numbers, right?
我们再来一次
So let's again,
让我们调用该算法来了解在封面下实际发生了什么。
let's invoke that algorithm to see what
is actually happening under the covers.
去感受双重平等的意义
To get a sense of what
double equals is doing.
首先，它尝试比较 workshoplCount 和 workshop2Count。
First, it tries to compare
workshop1Count and workshop2Count.
那是 ==
That's the ==.
它将 workshoplCount 转换为其基本形式，即其编号。
It turns workshop1Count into its
primitive form, which is its number.
但是 workshop2Count 是一个数组，所以它首先执行的是 toPrimitive。
But workshop2Count is an array, so
what it first does is say toPrimitive.
对数组的 toPrimitive 有什么影响 ?
What happens to
the toPrimitive of an array?
它会让自己干干干死所以我们最终以第 5 行
It stringifies itself, so
then we end up with line 5,
42 == "42" ，对吗 ?
42 == "42", right?
但那是因为那个奇怪的阵列
But that’s only because of that
weird array stringification
不包含方括号的内容。
that doesn’t include the brackets.
所以它几乎是意外地在这里工作。
So it’s almost accidentally working here.
由于阵列中只有一个值，因此仅意外地工作。
And only accidentally working because
there is only one value in the array.
你和我一起吗
You with me?
现在我们有两种不同的类型，我们有一个数字和一个字符串。
Now we have two different types,
we have a number and a string.
这里有两个选择
There's two options here.
我们要么把数字变成一个字符串
We could either make
the number into a string and
比较字符串，或将字符串设置为数字并比较数字。
compare the strings, or make the string
into a number and compare the numbers.
算法中哪个发生了
Which one happens in the algorithm?
它倾向于- >> 扬声器 2: 数字化。
It prefers-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Numerification.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 数字比较，因此字符串将成为数字，并且
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Numeric comparison,
so the string becomes the number, and
请注意，第 6 行，第 3 行等于 3 ，因为现在的类型相同。
notice here, line 6, it does a triple
equals because the types are now the same.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 你遵循这一推理吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: You follow
that line of reasoning?
这显然是一个典型的例子，但是
Now this is obviously a contrived example,
but
问题是即使有用也不代表你应该用它
the point here is that even if it works,
that doesn't mean you should use it.
这是我认为最明显的例子之一
This is one of those
clear examples I think
在那里胁迫对我们来说是件坏事
where coercion is a very bad thing for us.
您应该缩小面积，不要在数字之间进行比较，
You should reduce the surface area and
not make comparisons between numbers and
数字的数组。
arrays of numbers.
这甚至在编程上都没有意义。
That doesn't even make
any sense in programming.
而这正是我们被咬的大部分角落的地方
And yet that's where most of our corner
cases that we get bitten by are,
因为我们都做了这些多态的打字
because we do all of that
polymorphic typing stuff.
我们不应该这样做。
We should never do that.
您不应该通过使用三重等号来解决此问题。
And you shouldn't fix this
problem by using triple equals.
好的，这里最重要的是，这里的修订是不使用三重等号。
Okay, most important take-away here,
the fix here is not to use triple equals.
三等号能防止你看到真正的问题
Triple equals prevents you
from seeing the real problem,
这就是你第一次做的比较糟糕的对比
which is that you're making a terrible
comparison in the first place.
您应该做的是修正它，从而使您所做的比较有意义。
What you should do is fix it so that the
comparisons that you're making make sense.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 是的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yes.
>> 演讲者 3: 我的意思是，我知道你这样做是为了说明一点，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: I mean, I understand
you did this to demonstrate a point,
但如果我能看到这样的代码
but if I would look at code like this,
你不会说那个人有更大的问题吗
wouldn't you say that that person
has bigger problems than that?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这正是我的意思。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That's exactly my point.
>> 演讲者 3: 是的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Yeah.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这里有更大的问题。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: There
are bigger problems here.
这不是一个，你应该用这个双等号。
This is not a,
you should go use double equals this way.
这就是人们抱怨的双重平等
This is, this is what people
complain about with double equals,
他们说双重等于是问题
and they're saying that
double equals is the problem.
真正的问题是你做了一个非感性的对比。
And the real problem is that you're
making a nonsensical comparison.
双重平等不是你的错
Double equals isn't
the one that's at fault.
而三重等于只覆盖它，它没有解决真正的问题。
And triple equals only covers it up,
it doesn't fix the real problem.
如果你做出合理的比较
If you make sensible comparisons,
就像一个数字的字符串表示实际数字，
like a string representation of
a number to the actual number,
这是一个明智的对比和胁迫在那里完全有道理。
that's a sensible comparison and
coercion makes complete sense there.
但如果你把某样东西完全不同
But if you compare something to
something entirely different and
不小心工作太不理智了
it accidentally works,
that's not sensible.
这不太合理
That's not reasonable.
我同意你的看法，我们看到的结果是，你为什么要这样做 ?
I agree with you that the outcome that
we see is, why would you do that?
但我不喜欢的是说 JavaScript 在这里设计不好
But what I don't tend to do is say
JavaScript was poorly designed here.
有历史原因
There are historical reasons for
为什么它甚至可以允许两个图元进行比较。
why it allowed even the two
primitives in a comparison.
如果我在设计这种胁迫的话我就会把所有其他的强迫
If I were designing the coercion, I would
of done all the other coercions but
不包括这两个原语，因为在我看来
not included the two primitives,
because in my opinion the only kind of
非原始比较应该是可能的，这是身份比较。
non-primitive comparison that should ever
be possible is the identity comparison.
用原语进行胁迫是疯狂的。
Coercion with primitives is crazy.
但以图元胁迫的历史原因之一就是
But one of the historical reasons for
the coercion with primitives is that in
你做了新字符串的时候，现在你有了一个对象。
the olden days you did newString,
and now you have an object.
但你不认为它是一个物体
But you don't think of
it as being an object,
你认为它是原始的
you think of it as being the primitive.
所以他们允许那个非原始的人强迫
So they allowed that non-primitive
to coercively down coerce
它的原始当量
itself to its primitive equivalent.
这就是为什么算法有类似的东西。
That's why the algorithm
has something like that.
我不会写那个代码但这就是为什么
I wouldn't write that code,
but that's why it's there.
我认为这很难说这是一个糟糕的设计。
So it's hard to say that's a poor design,
in my opinion.